<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:mtree="http://www.mosets.com/tree/rss/">
<channel>
<title>OpenFoundry - Recently Added Listings - 介紹</title>
<description></description>
<link>https://www.openfoundry.org/</link>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 02:33:48 +0100</lastBuildDate>
<generator>FeedCreator 1.7.3</generator>
<item>
	<title>PHP</title>
	<link>https://www.openfoundry.org/en/resourcecatalog/Program-Development/Programming-Languages/php/Introduction/php</link>
	<description><![CDATA[<p>
<p>PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor is a widely used, general-purpose scripting language that was originally designed for web development to produce dynamic web pages. For this purpose, PHP code is embedded into the HTML source document and interpreted by a web server with a PHP processor module, which generates the web page document. As a general-purpose programming language, PHP code is processed by an interpreter application in command-line mode performing desired operating system operations and producing program output on its standard output channel. It may also function as a graphical application. PHP is available as a processor for most modern web servers and as a standalone interpreter on most operating systems and computing platforms.</p>
<p>PHP was originally created by Rasmus Lerdorf in 1995 and has been in continuous development ever since. The main implementation of PHP is now produced by the PHP Group and serves as the de facto standard for PHP as there is no formal specification.PHP is free software released under the PHP License.</p>
<p>PHP includes free and open source libraries with the core build. PHP is a fundamentally Internet-aware system with modules built in for accessing FTP servers, many database servers, embedded SQL libraries such as embedded PostgreSQL, MySQL and SQLite, LDAP servers, and others. Many functions familiar to C programmers such as those in the stdio family are available in the standard PHP build.</p>
<p>Platform:Cross platform;  License:PHP License</p>
<p>Reference:<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PHP" target="_blank">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PHP </a></p>
</p>]]></description>
	<author>dio</author>
	<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 02:07:16 +0100</pubDate>
	<guid>https://www.openfoundry.org/en/resourcecatalog/Program-Development/Programming-Languages/php/Introduction/php</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
